From the minute I wake, early in the morning,
أستيقظ باكراً في الصباح
my eyes barely open,
وبالكاد أستطيع أن أفتح عينَيّ.
I take off my pajamas and put on my work uniform.
أخلع لباس النوم وأرتدي زيّ العمل.
I begin with the huge balcony.
أبدأ بالشرفة الضخمة.
I lean out on the very edge, holding onto the railings.
أقف على حافة الشرفة، مُتمسِّكةً بالدرابزين.
Because the house is huge,
وبما أن المنزل كبير جدّاً،
I finish cleaning the living room around 9:30.
أنتهي من تنظيف الصالون حوالي الساعة 9:30.
Meanwhile, Madam wakes up,
في هذا الوقت تقريباً، تستيقظ المدام.
and I prepare her coffee.
أحضِّر لها القهوة.
Then I get back to work.
ثم أتابع عملي.
First, I clean Madam’s en suite bathroom,
أبدأ بحمام غرفة المدام،
before Mister’s, because he wakes up later.
قبل أن أنتقل إلى حمام غرفة الميستر لأنه يستيقظ بعدها.
The bathroom is hard to clean, it’s all glass.
تنظيف الحمام صعب، فهو مُزجَّج بالكامل
As soon as I finish,
ما إن أنتهي من كل ذلك،
while their daughter is still asleep,
وفيما ابنتهم لا تزال نائمة،
I tidy her room very quietly.
أبدأ بترتيب غرفتها بهدوء كبير...
Then, when that’s finished,
ما إن أنتهي من كل ذلك،
I enter the kitchen.
أعود إلى المطبخ.
I’ve barely finished preparing to eat before it’s breakfast time.
بالكاد أنتهي من تحضير الطعام حتّى يكون وقت الإفطار قد حلّ.
I set the table for the whole family,
أُعِدُّ المائدة للعائلة كلها،
and go to wake up the daughter.
ثم أذهب لإيقاظ الابنة.
When she’s finally up
وبعدما تستيقظ أخيراً،
I prepare her Nescafé.
أحضِّر لها الـ"نسكافيه".
Then she breakfasts with everyone.
ثم تتناول طعامها مع العائلة.